What? It can actually be 100% popular! The new event Treasure Month will start on August 8th.
Show the treasure map to get the treasure location. Go to the treasure location and turn in the treasure map to get the treasure.
Among them, treasure No. 8 must be red.
There are three ways to obtain treasure maps: the first is that treasure map clues can be exchanged for treasure maps;
The second type can be opened by touching specific courage;
The third type has a probability of dropping after defeating the invading Hafk team. If you think it’s still too difficult to obtain the method,
What to do? I have a plan.
Just call our good brothers and just sit back and wait at Treasure Point No. 8.
Treasure No. 8 of Dam Zero is in the container area, and Treasure No. 8 of Bakeshi is in the Tower of Babel.
Treasure No. 8 in Longbow Valley is on the upper right side of Galbijo. If the video is useful to you,
Don't forget to click follow.